About Me

I am a Software Engineer with over 5 years of experience in web development. I began my career in 2016 after completing high school. Currently, I am seeking new opportunities to integrate my knowledge in Acoustic Engineering with Software Engineering.

During my bachelor's degree, I gained expertise in acoustic concepts such as DSP, Psychoacoustics, Auralization, among others. My final project involved utilizing the Web Audio API to develop a web system for convolving two signals and creating a platform for real-time auralizations, comparing results with Matlab.

Skills

- Matlab;
- Python;
- C/C++ (basic use);
- HTML/CSS;
- PHP/Laravel;
- Javascript;
- Docker;
- Golang; (Learning)

Giuliano G. Arnhold

Software/Acoustic Engineer giuliarnhold@gmail.com - Brazil

Education

2012 - 2015

Technical course in computer science integrated into high school

Federal Institute of Science and Technology of Rio Grande do Sul (Brazil)

2016 - 2023

Acoustic Engineering

Federal University of Santa Maria (Brazil)

Work Experience

Software Engineer MD Móveis LTDA | 2020 - 2023

- Responsible for integrate internal ERP with diferrent ecommerce systems;
- Responsible for successfully automated critical business processes, resulting in substantial cost reductions;
- Revolutionizing data accuracy and empowering data-driven decision-making processes.

Software Engineer Rasys | 2023 - present

- Served as a mentor and technical leader for junior developers;
- Implement new technologies based on the company needs;